<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on Damitha Gunawardena @damithag</title><link>https://www.damitha.xyz/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on Damitha Gunawardena @damithag</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.damitha.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Creating a New Theme</title><link>https://www.damitha.xyz/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.damitha.xyz/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</guid><description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description></item><item><title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title><link>https://www.damitha.xyz/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.damitha.xyz/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid><description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description></item><item><title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title><link>https://www.damitha.xyz/posts/goisforlovers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.damitha.xyz/posts/goisforlovers/</guid><description>Hugo uses the excellent Go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in Go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using Go templates.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with Hugo</title><link>https://www.damitha.xyz/posts/hugoisforlovers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.damitha.xyz/posts/hugoisforlovers/</guid><description>Step 1. Install Hugo Go to Hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your OS and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at Install Hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
Clone the Hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313 Corresponding pseudo commands:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.damitha.xyz/docs/coding/alexa-i-cannot-hear-you/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.damitha.xyz/docs/coding/alexa-i-cannot-hear-you/</guid><description>just in time loudness enhancer So you have an old audio streaming workflow which isn&amp;rsquo;t quite loud enough for things like alexa or google home? An you want to increase the loudness without screwing up rest of the workflow?
why? More devices, more ways to stream content. No real standard to keep audio consistent across platforms. EBU is trying change that with R128
Want to learn more about it? I am no expert so will leave it to experts.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.damitha.xyz/docs/hobby-projects/automated-cabling-diagrams/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.damitha.xyz/docs/hobby-projects/automated-cabling-diagrams/</guid><description>hate drawing diagrams My side kick is managing the church av system, and state of the current cabling is bit of a mess when I took over. I tried to make sense out of the current cabling by meticulous documenting each cable.
The spreadsheet looked something like this.
I wanted to create something like this from that.
But I hate doing things that will become obsolete after the next gig.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.damitha.xyz/docs/hobby-projects/smart-home/intro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.damitha.xyz/docs/hobby-projects/smart-home/intro/</guid><description>intro After six years moving to the new house, the garage door remote finally decided to give up.</description></item></channel></rss>