<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on Damitha Gunawardena @damithag</title><link>https://www.damitha.xyz/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on Damitha Gunawardena @damithag</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.damitha.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://www.damitha.xyz/docs/coding/alexa-i-cannot-hear-you/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.damitha.xyz/docs/coding/alexa-i-cannot-hear-you/</guid><description>just in time loudness enhancer So you have an old audio streaming workflow which isn&amp;rsquo;t quite loud enough for things like alexa or google home? An you want to increase the loudness without screwing up rest of the workflow?
why? More devices, more ways to stream content. No real standard to keep audio consistent across platforms. EBU is trying change that with R128
Want to learn more about it? I am no expert so will leave it to experts.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.damitha.xyz/docs/coding/tracing-chromecast-traffic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.damitha.xyz/docs/coding/tracing-chromecast-traffic/</guid><description>Tracing Chromecast traffic via Mac Had problem at work where we need to see debug Chromecast streaming traffic. Chromecast doesn&amp;rsquo;t allow us to change network config manually. Thus needed to force traffic via default gateway where I was able to run mitmproxy
Having the abiliy to provide DHCP leases dnsmasq provides the ability to do that. Quite a simple config
brew install dnsmasq dnsmasq config dhcp-range=10.0.0.32,10.0.0.248,255.255.255.0,2h # Gateway dhcp-option=3,10.0.0.4 # DNS (This is where your transparent proxy runs ) dhcp-option=6,10.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.damitha.xyz/docs/hobby-projects/automated-cabling-diagrams/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.damitha.xyz/docs/hobby-projects/automated-cabling-diagrams/</guid><description>hate drawing diagrams My side kick is managing the church av system, and state of the current cabling is bit of a mess when I took over. I tried to make sense out of the current cabling by meticulous documenting each cable.
The spreadsheet looked something like this.
I wanted to create something like this from that.
But I hate doing things that will become obsolete after the next gig.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.damitha.xyz/docs/hobby-projects/smart-home/intro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.damitha.xyz/docs/hobby-projects/smart-home/intro/</guid><description>intro After six years moving to the new house, the garage door remote finally decided to give up.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.damitha.xyz/docs/wishlist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.damitha.xyz/docs/wishlist/</guid><description>stuff I want to do Wishlist</description></item></channel></rss>